Guide to the Archives of Irish America Newspapers and Periodicals Collection AIA 004
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- II: Periodicals, 1881-2008
  - Keltoi: A Pan-Celtic Review, 1986-1987, 1990 (Box 164, Folder 17)
  - Lies of Our Times: British Terror in Northern Ireland, Oct 1990 (Box 164, Folder 18)
  - Nation, The (Ho Ho Kus, NJ), 1985-1989 (Box 164, Folder 19)
  - Nation, The (Ho Ho Kus, NJ), 1990 (Box 164, Folder 20)
  - Nation, The (Ho Ho Kus, NJ), 1991 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Nation, The (Ho Ho Kus, NJ), 1992 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Nation, The (Ho Ho Kus, NJ), 1993 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Nation, The (Ho Ho Kus, NJ), 1994 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Nation, The (Ho Ho Kus, NJ), 1995 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Nua Eabhrac, 1981-1981 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - The Recorder: Bulletin of the American Irish Historical Society. (New York), 1932-1970, 1988; Holdings: 1932, Vol, 5, no. 5; 1933, Vol. 6, nos. 2-4; 1934, Vol. 7, nos. 1-3; 1935 Vol. 8, no. 1; 1936 Vol. 9, nos. 1-4; 1939 Vol. 10, no. 1-2, 6; 1950, Vol. 12, no. 1; 1951 Vol. 13, no. 1; 1952, Vol. 14; 1953 Vol. 15; 1954, Vol. 16; 1955 Vol. 16; 1963, Vol. 24; 1964, Vol. 26; 1965, Vol. 28; 1966, Vol. 29; 1967, Vol. 30; 1968, VOl. 31; 1970. Vol. 33; Supplesment to 1988 "In Memoriam Darcy O'Brien;" List of Publications, 1898-1943 [from 1952 on it looks like only one bulletin was published per annum] (Box 167)
    Scope and Content Note
    Holdings: 1932, Vol, 5, no. 5; 1933, Vol. 6, nos. 2-4; 1934, Vol. 7, nos. 1-3; 1935 Vol. 8, no. 1; 1936 Vol. 9, nos. 1-4; 1939 Vol. 10, no. 1-2, 6; 1950, Vol. 12, no. 1; 1951 Vol. 13, no. 1; 1952, Vol. 14; 1953 Vol. 15; 1954, Vol. 16; 1955 Vol. 16; 1963, Vol. 24; 1964, Vol. 26; 1965, Vol. 28; 1966, Vol. 29; 1967, Vol. 30; 1968, VOl. 31; 1970. Vol. 33; Supplesment to 1988 "In Memoriam Darcy O'Brien;" List of Publications, 1898-1943 [from 1952 on it looks like only one bulletin was published per annum]
  - Republican Bulletin / Iris na Poblachta (Dublin) Vol. 1, nos. 1-3, 1987 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Saoirse': Irish Freedom, 1987-1997 (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - Shamrock Leaf, 1990-1996 (Box 165, Folder 9)
  - Shanachie, The, 1990-2000 (Box 165, Folder 10)
  - Spirit of Freedom, 1986-1987 (Box 165, Folder 11)
  - Spirit of Freedom, 1988 (Box 165, Folder 12)
  - Spirit of Freedom, 1989 (Box 165, Folder 13)
  - University College Dublin Alumni Newsletter, Jun 1989-Jan 1993 (Box 165, Folder 14)
  - University College Dublin Alumni Magazine, 1993-1994 (Box 165, Folder 15)
  - University College Dublin Alumni Magazine, 1995-2000 (Box 165, Folder 16)
  - World of Hibernia, 1995 (Box 165, Folder 17)
  - World of Hibernia, 1995-1996 (Box 165, Folder 18)
  - World of Hibernia, 1996 (Box 165, Folder 19)
  - World of Hibernia, 1996-1997 (Box 165, Folder 20)
  - World of Hibernia, 1997 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - World of Hibernia, Spr 1998 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - World of Hibernia, Sum 1998-Aut 1998 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - World of Hibernia, 1998-1999 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - World of Hibernia, 1999 (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - World of Hibernia, Spr 2000 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - World of Hibernia, Sum 2000-Win 2000 (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - World of Hibernia, Spr 2001 (Box 166, Folder 8)
  - World of Hibernia, Win 2001 (Box 166, Folder 9)